

# GINELLE GRACE N. ARANETA

# Developer

An innovative developer with 3 years of experience, in developing and implementing software solutions that drive revenue growth and increase customer satisfaction. Capable of working with a variety of technology and software solutions and managing databases. Exceptional skills in software testing and technical documentation and a history of successful contributions in the field.



ginellegracearaneta@gmail.com



+639308311989



O City of San Pedro, Laguna, Philippines

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Jr Developer**

OLVRO Co. Ltd. WATSON PERSONAL CARE STORE (PHILS) INC. 01/2023 - 05/2024

- Collaborated with a team of developers to develop and enhance the assigned project.
- Technical documentation, implementation, monitoring, and tracking of new requirements for the project.
- Analyzed systems administration tools and programming input to help improve the software design of a product.
- Assigning tasks to all testing team members and ensuring that they have sufficient work to do on the project.
- Constructed workflow documents before beginning a new project in order to map out program design and ideas visually.
- Accountability on the UAT signoff.
- · Administrative Works.

## Jr Developer

PRIMOVER CONSULTANCY SERVICES INC. WATSON PERSONAL CARE STORE (PHILS) INC. 01/2022 - 12/2022

- Collaborated with a team of developers to develop and enhance the assigned project.
- Technical documentation, implementation, monitoring, and tracking of new requirements for the project.
- Analyzed systems administration tools and programming input to help improve the software design of a product.
- Assigning tasks to all testing team members and ensuring that they have sufficient work to do on the project.
- Constructed workflow documents before beginning a new project in order to map out program design and ideas visually.
- Accountability on the UAT signoff.
- · Administrative Works.

#### Programmer

ByteApp Solutions Inc. 08/2022 - 10/2022

- Develop, design and update software database and test and implement new programs.
- Ensure the timely delivery of the different testing milestones. Accountability on the UAT signoff.

### **Applications Specialist**

ACLT Computing Inc. 03/2022 - 05/2022

- Maintaining the optimal performance of system applications.
- Implement and supporting different versions of software.
- Technical Documentation.

### Jr. Developer/Technical Writer

WE SUPPORT INC.

WATSON PERSONAL CARE STORE (PHILS) INC.

06/2021 - 12/2021

- Collaborated with a team of developers to develop and enhance the assigned project.
- Technical documentation, implementation, monitoring, and tracking of new requirements for the project.
- Analyzed systems administration tools and programming input to help improve the software design of a product.
- Assigning tasks to all testing team members and ensuring that they have sufficient work to do on the project.
- Constructed workflow documents before beginning a new project in order to map out program design and ideas visually.

## Branch Manager

RD Pawnshop, Inc. 07/2019 - 03/2020

- Checks daily reports such as Loans Extended, Loans Paid, Cashier's Report and Sales Report.
- Responsible of all accounting reportorial requirements in the branch.

#### PROJECT INVOLVED -

PetKonek PH

A pet application platform that will revolutionize the way we manage our pets that we can monitor or record the events or appointments of our pets.

MyPrimeHR HRIS
(Human Resource Information System)

MyPrimeHR is a full web version for cloud computing infrastructure. They can perform all sorts of allowable inquiries, record viewing, online filing, submission of requests and applications, and approvals of superiors.

WVAS RESBAKUNA COVID19 Registration

An Online Registration for RESBAKUNA COVID19 Booster Shot Customers. It has an email notification on customer booking and an internal report generation for branch and HO.

**WRAS Project** 

Data Management and internal reports that supports the data and information in organizations.

**WVAS Project** 

Web application for scheduling of vaccination to clients, it has a report generator to know the appointment for each branch.

# **SKILLS**

- Agile methodologies (Scrum, Kanban)
- Programming languages (C#, ASP.NET MVC)
- Web development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript)
- Database management (SQL)
- Git/version control (GitHub)
- Automated testing (NUnit)

- Visual Studio
- SharePoint
- Figma
- Jira
- User interface (UI) design
- Technical documentation

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

St. Louis Anne Colleges 2015 - 2019

Captsone Project: Adelan Hardware Store Management System